pixable.com 2010-09-13

# Pixable, print your Facebook content!

Pixable's Privacy Policy

**This policy is effective July 1, 2009.  **

Pixable’s Privacy Policy is designed to help you:

  * **1)** Understand what information we collect and how we collect, share, and use the information; and

  * **2)** Make informed decisions when using the services located at www.Pixable.com (“Pixable” or “Web Site”)

By using or accessing Pixable, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy, as modified by us from time to time.

The Information We Collect

When you visit Pixable, you provide us with two types of information:

  * **1) Personal Information**  that you knowingly choose to disclose through various Web Site features.

  * **2) Web Site Use Information**  that is collected by us as you interact with our Web Site.

Personal Information You Provide to Us

**1)** We collect "Personal Information" that you submit to us voluntarily through our Web Site:

  * **2)** When you register with Pixable, you provide certain Personal Information, including your name, email address, and password. 

  * **3)** When you create a profile on the Web Site after registering, you may provide material that may contain Personal Information, such as a personal photo, email address, or a “headline.”

  * **4)** When you post any material (such as User Content) on the Web Site, you may be providing Personal Information.

  * **5)** When you order products or services on Pixable, you provide Personal Information necessary to complete the transaction, including your name, credit card information, shipping information and billing information.

  * **6)** When you contact us to give feedback or ask a question using the forms on the Web Site, you provide your name, email address and your comment, question or feedback.

  * **7)** When you participate in our surveys, we may collect additional Personal Information.

  * **8)** When you contact us by sending us an email, we will collect your email address, any Personal Information contained in the email, and any Personal Information attached to the email.

Web Site Use Information

When you access Pixable, we collect non-personally-identifiable information including your browser type, operating system, domain names, and IP Address.  We use different types of technologies to collect this information, including single-pixel GIFs. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using “cookies.” A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user.  We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in.  These cookies terminate when the user closes the browser.  Under other circumstances, including if you select the “Remember Me” option upon login, we use a persistent cookie, for example, to store your login ID (but not your password) to allow you to automatically login when you come back to Pixable. You can set your browser to refuse cookies; however, if you do so, some or all of the Web Site may not function properly or at all.

User Content and Other Information

When you use Pixable, you may form relationships, send messages, perform searches and queries, and transmit Personal Information through various channels.  We collect Personal Information related to these services so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features.  In most cases, we retain the Personal Information so that, for instance, you can view a list of your friends or see the books you are currently contributing to.  When you update your Personal Information, we sometimes keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information.

You post Personal Information in User Content (as defined in Pixable's [ _Terms of Use_](http://www.pixable.com/terms)) on the Web Site at your own risk.  Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your books, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.  We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your books and Personal Information.  Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Web Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.  We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Web Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your User Content.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on Pixable is a violation of the Pixable Terms of Use and should be reported to [_privacy@Pixable.com_](mailto:privacy@pixable.com).

If you choose to use our invitation service to tell friends about our Web Site or invite them to collaborate on a book, we will ask you for your friend’s email address.  Your friend will automatically be sent a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Web Site. Pixable stores information gathered during this process to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [ _info@Pixable.com_](mailto:info@pixable.com) to request that we remove your friend's information from our database.

By using Pixable, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.

Use of Information Obtained by Pixable

In general, information you submit to us is used either to respond to requests that you make or to aid us in serving you better, including to fix technical problems, provide administrative services, and monitor traffic, the number of visitors, and the effectiveness of programs.  We may use aggregated user data to market the Web Site to others.  We may provide these services ourselves or share the information with partners who will provide the services for us.

We may use your Personal Information to provide you with newsletters and surveys and to notify you of important changes to the Web Site, new services, and special offers.  If you do not want to receive such email notices, you may login to your account at the Web Site and opt out of receiving such email or send email to [ _privacy@Pixable.com_](mailto:privacy@pixable.com) or mail to Privacy, Pixable, 12th Floor, 160 Varick Sreet, New York, NY 10013. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, or special offers.  If we have provided any third party with your information, you will have to contact the third-party directly with any opt-out request. 

Profile information is used by Pixable primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access Pixable and to be presented to others you permit to view that information.

Your name, headline, a thumbnail of your photo, and thumbnails of your most recent books will be available in search results across Pixable to allow your friends to find you and send a friend request.  People who see your name in searches will be able to access your profile or other personal information.

User Content in your profile, including the books you create or contribute to, will be displayed to users with whom you have a relationship through your profile, search results and various other pages on the Web Site.  In addition, the title, page count, thumbnail photo, description, author and list of contributors of your books will be visible to all users of Pixable depending on the privacy settings of those books.  If your book is set to be viewable by only your friends or only a specific list of users, it will not appear in search results by people who do not have permission to view it.

Pixable will send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service.  For instance, if a friend sends you a new message or you receive a request to collaborate on a friend’s book, you may receive an email alerting you to that fact.

**Feedback**

If you provide feedback on any of our products and services to us, we may use such feedback for any purpose, provided we will not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. Pixable will collect any information contained in such communication and will treat the Personal Information in such communication in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Children Under Age 13

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) defines personal information as "individually identifiable information," including things like a first and last name, a street address, an email address, or a telephone number. COPPA places requirements on websites that collect such information from children. You must be at least 13 years or older to register and use this Service. If you are under the age of 13, you must use an account created by a parent or guardian, and you must have the explicit permission of a parent or guardian to use the Service.

**Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18**

We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the internet.

Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

Pixable is all about collaborating and sharing information with others – your friends on the Web Site and people you share it with.  We allow you to choose privacy settings for the books you create with your friends on the Web Site. These settings allow you to make an informed choice about who has access to the information and content that you create on or upload to the Web Site.  We do not sell your Personal Information to third party marketers without your permission. We share your Personal Information with third parties only in limited circumstances.  We comply with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 and intend to do business only with companies that also comply.   **We will not sell your Personal Information to anyone we think is a spammer.**

Unlike most sites on the Web, Pixable limits access to Web Site information by third party search engine “crawlers” (e.g., Google, Yahoo, MSN, Ask). The Web Site is set up to block access by these engines to personal information beyond your name, profile picture and headline.

We may provide collected information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about Pixable, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services, to print the books that you order, or to provide search results or links. In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your Personal Information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities.  Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any Personal Information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to Pixable-specified purposes.  If we provide any of the information collected from you with a third party, their use of that information will be governed by their privacy policy. 

For example: when you place an order for a printed copy of a book on Pixable, your billing information is transmitted to a third-party credit card processor and your shipping information is transmitted to third-party printer to be printed, bound and shipped to you.

We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas, law enforcement investigations, or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws.  We also may release information to protect its rights, property, or other interests, including those of its customers or other third parties or to prevent illegal activities or violations of the Pixable Terms of Use.  This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents, or government agencies.

If the ownership of all or substantially all of the Pixable business, or individual business units owned by Interactive Memories, Inc., were to change, information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations.  We may also transfer information if we partner with another company.

Links

Pixable may contain links to other web sites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Web Site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected via Pixable.

Changing or Removing Information

Access and control over most Personal Information on Pixable is readily available through your account settings.  Pixable users may modify or remove their information through the  _My Account_  page.  Information will be updated immediately.

If you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals on Pixable(e.g., sending a message), you generally cannot remove or edit such communications. Pixable may delete your information from its system, at its sole discretion, at any time.

Security

Pixable takes precautions to protect our users’ Personal Information; however, no precautions are 100% effective.  As a result, Pixable does not guarantee that Personal Information you provide to us will remain secure.  Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any questions about the security of the Pixable Web Site, please contact us at [ _privacy@Pixable.com_](mailto:privacy@pixable.com).

Terms of Use, Notice and Revisions

If you choose to visit Pixable, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to the then-current Privacy Policy and our [ _Terms of Use_](http://www.pixable.com/terms), including limitations and damages, arbitration of, and application of law of the state of California.  We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time by posting any changes on the Web Site. All changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Web Site.  If we make changes, we will indicate at the top of the page the policy’s effective date. We therefore encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Your use of the Web Site after any changes to the Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of the new Privacy Policy.  Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

Contacting Pixable

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [ _privacy@Pixable.com_](mailto:privacy@pixable.com).
